{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "If you _____ plants, they will grow faster .",
      "correctAnswer": "water",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will water"
    },
    {
      "question": "If it _____ tomorrow, I'll take the car .",
      "correctAnswer": "rains",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you _____ hard, you will pass your exams .",
      "correctAnswer": "study",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will study"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I _____ too much coffee, I will not sleep at night .",
      "correctAnswer": "drink",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "When I _____ work, I'll call you .",
      "correctAnswer": "finish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will finish"
    },
    {
      "question": "We will go to the restaurant if the babysitter _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "arrives",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will arrive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I will stay in London if I _____ a job .",
      "correctAnswer": "get",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will get"
    },
    {
      "question": "I will give you a key if I _____ at home .",
      "correctAnswer": "am not",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will not be"
    },
    {
      "question": "You will go to the party if you _____ homework .",
      "correctAnswer": "finish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will finish"
    },
    {
      "question": "I will take a cat if I _____ a flat .",
      "correctAnswer": "buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "If the weather is fine, we _____ for a walk .",
      "correctAnswer": "will go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "go"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I get this job, I _____ a lot of money .",
      "correctAnswer": "will earn",
      "incorrectAnswers": "earn"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I go to London, I _____ the Tower of London .",
      "correctAnswer": "will see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "see"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you don’t hurry, we _____ the train .",
      "correctAnswer": "will miss",
      "incorrectAnswers": "miss"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he is having a meeting at the moment, I _____ him later .",
      "correctAnswer": "will call",
      "incorrectAnswers": "call"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ a university if she passes her test .",
      "correctAnswer": "will enter",
      "incorrectAnswers": "enters"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ learn English if you want to live abroad .",
      "correctAnswer": "will have to",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have to"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ her everything if she calls .",
      "correctAnswer": "will tell",
      "incorrectAnswers": "tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ a cold if you don't wear a scarf .",
      "correctAnswer": "will catch",
      "incorrectAnswers": "catch"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ happy if you give her flowers .",
      "correctAnswer": "will be",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "If you _____ # plants, they will grow faster .",
      "correctAnswer": "water",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will water"
    },
    {
      "question": "If it _____ # tomorrow, I'll take the car .",
      "correctAnswer": "rains",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will rain"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you _____ # hard, you will pass your exams .",
      "correctAnswer": "study",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will study"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I _____ # too much coffee, I will not sleep at night .",
      "correctAnswer": "drink",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will drink"
    },
    {
      "question": "When I _____ # work, I'll call you .",
      "correctAnswer": "finish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will finish"
    },
    {
      "question": "We will go to the restaurant if the babysitter _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "arrives",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will arrive"
    },
    {
      "question": "I will stay in London if I _____ # a job .",
      "correctAnswer": "get",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will get"
    },
    {
      "question": "I will give you a key if I _____ # at home .",
      "correctAnswer": "am not",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will not be"
    },
    {
      "question": "You will go to the party if you _____ # homework .",
      "correctAnswer": "finish",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will finish"
    },
    {
      "question": "I will take a cat if I _____ # a flat .",
      "correctAnswer": "buy",
      "incorrectAnswers": "will buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "If the weather is fine, we _____ # for a walk .",
      "correctAnswer": "will go",
      "incorrectAnswers": "go"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I get this job, I _____ # a lot of money .",
      "correctAnswer": "will earn",
      "incorrectAnswers": "earn"
    },
    {
      "question": "If I go to London, I _____ # the Tower of London .",
      "correctAnswer": "will see",
      "incorrectAnswers": "see"
    },
    {
      "question": "If you don’t hurry, we _____ # the train .",
      "correctAnswer": "will miss",
      "incorrectAnswers": "miss"
    },
    {
      "question": "If he is having a meeting at the moment, I _____ # him later .",
      "correctAnswer": "will call",
      "incorrectAnswers": "call"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ # a university if she passes her test .",
      "correctAnswer": "will enter",
      "incorrectAnswers": "enters"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ # learn English if you want to live abroad .",
      "correctAnswer": "will have to",
      "incorrectAnswers": "have to"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # her everything if she calls .",
      "correctAnswer": "will tell",
      "incorrectAnswers": "tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ # a cold if you don't wear a scarf .",
      "correctAnswer": "will catch",
      "incorrectAnswers": "catch"
    },
    {
      "question": "She _____ # happy if you give her flowers .",
      "correctAnswer": "will be",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is"
    }
  ]
}